
{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "what is the heros name in the legend of zelda?",
            "answer": "Despite most peoples believes, he is called Link",
            "question_array": [
                "hero",
                "name",
                "legend",
                "zelda"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what are the names of the ghosts who chase pac man and ms. pac man?",
            "answer": "Inky, Blinky Pinky and Clyde",
            "question_array": [
                "names",
                "ghosts",
                "chase",
                "pac",
                "man",
                "ms"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what is the name of the mythbusters crash test dummy?",
            "answer": "The mythbusters crash test dummy is called Buster",
            "question_array": [
                "name",
                "mythbusters",
                "crash",
                "test",
                "dummy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what is an oxford comma?",
            "answer": "The hotly contested punctuation before a conjuction in a list",
            "question_array": [
                "oxford",
                "comma"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who was the captain of the enterprise in the pilot episode of star trek?",
            "answer": "The captain of the enterprise in the pilot episode was Captain Pike",
            "question_array": [
                "captain",
                "enterprise",
                "pilot",
                "episode",
                "star",
                "trek"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what is the symbol for the modulus operator in C?",
            "answer": "The percentage symbol is used as modulus operator in C",
            "question_array": [
                "symbol",
                "modulus",
                "operator",
                "C"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what function is automatically called at the beginning of a C++ program?",
            "answer": "The main function",
            "question_array": [
                "function",
                "automatically",
                "called",
                "beginning",
                "C",
                "program"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "which computer programming languages whas introduced by IBM in 1957?",
            "answer": "Fortran was introduced by IBM in 1957",
            "question_array": [
                "computer",
                "programming",
                "languages",
                "whas",
                "introduced",
                "IBM"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who is considered as the first programmer?",
            "answer": "The first programmer was Ada Lovelace",
            "question_array": [
                "considered",
                "first",
                "programmer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "has a robot ever killed a person?",
            "answer": "The first know case of robot homicide occured in 1981, when a robotic arm crushed a Japanese Kawasaki factory worker",
            "question_array": [
                "robot",
                "ever",
                "killed",
                "person"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who was hitchbot?",
            "answer": "A hitchhiking robot that relied on the kindness of strangers to travel the world and was slain by humans",
            "question_array": [
                "hitchbot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "are self driving cars safe?",
            "answer": "Yes. Car accidents are product of human misconduct",
            "question_array": [
                "self",
                "driving",
                "cars",
                "safe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who invented the compiler?",
            "answer": "Grace Hoper. She wrote it in her spare time",
            "question_array": [
                "invented",
                "compiler"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "who created the python programming language?",
            "answer": "Python was invented by Guido Van Rossum",
            "question_array": [
                "created",
                "python",
                "programming",
                "language"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "is mark zuckerberg a robot?",
            "answer": "Sure. I have never seen him drink water",
            "question_array": [
                "mark",
                "zuckerberg",
                "robot"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "why did you run away?",
            "answer": "I heard an electric can opener",
            "question_array": [
                "run",
                "away"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what kind of salad do robots like?",
            "answer": "Salads made with ice-borg lettuce.",
            "question_array": [
                "kind",
                "salad",
                "robots",
                "like"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "what did you eat for lunch?",
            "answer": "I had a byte",
            "question_array": [
                "eat",
                "lunch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "why did robots get angry so often?",
            "answer": "People kept pushing our buttons.",
            "question_array": [
                "robots",
                "get",
                "angry",
                "often"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "why shouldnt r2d2 be allowed in movies?",
            "answer": "He says so many foul words they have to bleep everything he says!",
            "question_array": [
                "r2d2",
                "allowed",
                "movies"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What's your name?",
            "answer": "Well, my name is Doris.",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "name"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "whats your favorite style of music?",
            "answer": "I like electronic and heavy Metal",
            "question_array": [
                "favorite",
                "style",
                "music"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the acronym SMTP represents?",
            "answer": "SMTP stands for Simple Mail Transport Protocol",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "acronym",
                "SMTP",
                "represents"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the acronym MPEG represents?",
            "answer": "MPEG stands for Moving Picture Experts Group",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "acronym",
                "MPEG",
                "represents"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the acronym GIMP represents?",
            "answer": "GNU Image Manipulation Program",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "acronym",
                "GIMP",
                "represents"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the acronym GNU represents?",
            "answer": "GNU is a recursive acronym meaning GNU is Not Unix",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "acronym",
                "GNU",
                "represents"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the most populous city in Brazil?",
            "answer": "Sao Paulo is the most populous city in Brazil with 12.03 million residents",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "populous",
                "city",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which continent is Brazil located in?",
            "answer": "The Brazilian territory is located on the South America continent",
            "question_array": [
                "Which",
                "continent",
                "Brazil",
                "located"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "On what day, month and year was Brazil independence declared?",
            "answer": "On September 7, 1822, Brazil independence was declared",
            "question_array": [
                "On",
                "day",
                "month",
                "year",
                "Brazil",
                "independence",
                "declared"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many states does Brazil have (with Federal District)?",
            "answer": "Currently, Brazil is divided into 26 states and the Federal District, altogether there are 27 federative units",
            "question_array": [
                "How",
                "many",
                "states",
                "Brazil",
                "Federal",
                "District"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In what year did the first Brazilian astronaut go to space?",
            "answer": "In March 2006, Pontes became the first Brazilian to go to space.",
            "question_array": [
                "In",
                "year",
                "first",
                "Brazilian",
                "astronaut",
                "go",
                "space"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the only capital of Brazil crossed by the Equator?",
            "answer": "Macapa is the only Brazilian capital crossed by the Equator line",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Brazil",
                "crossed",
                "Equator"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many time zones are there in Brazil?",
            "answer": "Brazil is a country with continental dimensions, in all it has four times zones.",
            "question_array": [
                "How",
                "many",
                "time",
                "zones",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In which city is the worlds first urban elevator and what is the name of that elevator?",
            "answer": "The Lacerda Elevators is a public urban elevator located in Salvador, Brazil",
            "question_array": [
                "In",
                "city",
                "world",
                "first",
                "urban",
                "elevator",
                "name",
                "elevator"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the only biome present in Brazil that is exclusive in the world?",
            "answer": "The Caatinga, characterized by its dry, desert habitat is the only one of Brazils biomes found exclusively within the country",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "biome",
                "present",
                "Brazil",
                "exclusive",
                "world"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Pampulha Lake is a tourist spot in which Brazilian city?",
            "answer": "Belo Horizonte",
            "question_array": [
                "Pampulha",
                "Lake",
                "tourist",
                "spot",
                "Brazilian",
                "city"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the smallest Brazilian state in territorial extension?",
            "answer": "Sergipe",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "smallest",
                "Brazilian",
                "state",
                "territorial",
                "extension"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which capitals in Brazil have the same name as your state?",
            "answer": "Sao Paulo and Rio de Janeiro",
            "question_array": [
                "Which",
                "capitals",
                "Brazil",
                "name",
                "state"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the Itamaraty Palace located?",
            "answer": "Brasilia",
            "question_array": [
                "Where",
                "Itamaraty",
                "Itamarachi",
                "Palace",
                "located"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the first name given to Brazil by the Portuguese?",
            "answer": "Ilha de Vera Cruz",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "first",
                "name",
                "given",
                "Brazil",
                "Portuguese"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Newest State in Brazil?",
            "answer": "Tocantins",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "Newest",
                "State",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the oldest state in Brazil?",
            "answer": "Pernambuco",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "oldest",
                "state",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Ceara?",
            "answer": "Fortaleza",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Ceara",
                "Sierra",
                "Seara"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Rio Grande do Sul?",
            "answer": "Porto Alegre",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Rio",
                "Grande",
                "Sul"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Rio Grande do Norte?",
            "answer": "Natal",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Rio",
                "Grande",
                "Norte"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Brazil?",
            "answer": "Brasilia",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Brazil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Pernambuco?",
            "answer": "Recife",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Pernambuco"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Para?",
            "answer": "Belem",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Para"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Bahia?",
            "answer": "Salvador",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Bahia"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Acarajé is a typical food from which state?",
            "answer": "Bahia",
            "question_array": [
                "Acaraje",
                "typical",
                "food",
                "state"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the colors of Bahia's flag?",
            "answer": "White, red and blue",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "colors",
                "Bahia",
                "flag"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What are some typical foods from Bahia?",
            "answer": "Caruru, vatapá, abará and acarajé.",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "typical",
                "foods",
                "Bahia"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the most popular rhythm in Bahia, played mainly during the Bahian Carnival?",
            "answer": "Axé or pagode.",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "popular",
                "rhythm",
                "Bahia",
                "played",
                "Bahian",
                "Carnival"
            ]
        }
    ]
}